Welcome back.
欢迎回来。
In the previous sections and also the little bit of this section until now, we have created classes, created
在前几节和本节的小部分内容中，我们已经创建了类，在其中创建了
methods in them, created instances of these classes called objects, and we invoked methods on these objects.
方法，创建了这些称为对象的类的实例，并对这些对象调用了方法。
We also learnt about primitive data types versus the reference types. From this video on,
我们还学习了原始数据类型和引用类型。从这个视频开始。
we would start exploring the inbuilt reference types in Java. In the next set of videos, we would be starting
我们将开始探索Java中内置的引用类型。在下一集视频中，我们将开始
to look at String, Wrapper classes, and also a few reference types to refer to it. In this video,
看一下字符串、封装类，以及一些引用类型的参考。在这个视频中。
let's start with the basics of the String class.
让我们从字符串类的基础知识开始。
Let's start with a simple question.
让我们从一个简单的问题开始。
We created a number of literals like this. With in double quotes, we said this is representing text.
我们创建了一些像这样的字词。用双引号，我们说这是代表文本。
One interesting thing to note about this strings is, actually this is a instance of a class called String.
关于这个字符串的一个有趣的事情是，实际上这是一个叫做String的类的实例。
How can I prove that?
我怎么能证明这一点呢？
All that you need to do is to say, "Test".length( ). Oops!, I am a little too early.
你只需要说，"Test".length( )。哎呀！，我有点太早了。
I just need to login into JShell first.
我只是需要先登录到JShell。
So, let's log into JShell before I would be able to execute the command.
所以，让我们在我能够执行命令之前登录到JShell。
Now I can execute "Test".length( ). I am in JShell right now and it's printing 4. This Test string has four
现在我可以执行 "Test".length( )。我现在就在JShell中，它正在打印4。这个Test字符串有四个
characters,
字符。
length is a method and Test is an instance, instance of what class? In Java, text is represented by a class
length是一个方法，Test是一个实例，什么类的实例？在Java中，文本是由一个叫做
called String.
叫做String。
If I want to store str as a Test, this is how we would do that.
如果我想把str存储为一个Test，我们将这样做。
So, String str = "Test" creates an instance of the Test and stores the reference of it in
所以，String str = "Test "创建了一个Test的实例，并把它的引用存储在
str. String
str。字符串
is very very special.
是非常非常特别的。
All the other objects you would need to do something like a new BigDecimal, right.
所有其他的对象你都需要做一些事情，比如新建一个BigDecimal，对吧。
So, when we did BigDecimal, we said BigDecimal bd = new BigDecimal of let's say 1.0.
所以，当我们做BigDecimal时，我们说BigDecimal bd = new BigDecimal of let's say 1.0。
So, we needed to use a constructor to create it.
所以，我们需要使用一个构造函数来创建它。
However with String, you don't really need to use a constructor. Even though if you would want str
但是对于字符串，你并不真的需要使用构造函数。尽管如果你想让str
=
you can do new String("Test").
你可以使用new String("Test")。
You can do that. But that's not really necessary.
你可以这样做。但这并不是真正必要的。
All that you need to do is String str = "Test" and that's more than sufficient. String
你所需要做的就是String str = "Test"，这就足够了。字符串
is a special class in Java.
是Java中的一个特殊类。
This Test is an instance of the class, String.
这个Test是String这个类的一个实例。
This is called a String literal.
这就是所谓的String literal。
We looked at the basic method which is present in here, length.
我们看了这里存在的基本方法，长度。
We'll start looking at a few other methods which are present in the String class to retrieve the details
我们将开始看一些其他的方法，这些方法存在于String类中，用于检索特定字符串的细节。
about a specific string, right. So, in String,
关于一个特定的字符串的细节，对吗。所以，在String中，索引从0开始。
the index starts with 0.
索引从0开始。
So, this is 0,
所以，这个是0。
this is 1, e is 1, s is 2, and t is 3.
这个是1，e是1，s是2，t是3。
So, if you want to get a specific character,
所以，如果你想得到一个特定的字符。
so let's say I would want to get the first character of a string,
比如说我想获得一个字符串的第一个字符。
the way I would need to do that is by saying str.charAt(0).
我需要做的是说str.charAt(0)。
The important thing is, the index starts with 0. So, 0, 1, 2, and 3.
重要的是，索引从0开始，所以，0、1、2、3。
So, let's quickly check another one str.charAt(2). It returns s. 0 is T, 1, and 2 is s.
那么，让我们快速检查另一个str.charAt(2)。它返回s。0是T，1，2是s。
str.CharAt(3),
str.CharAt(3)。
that's the last character.
那是最后一个字符。
Let's say I don't want to retrive one character but I would want to retrieve a substring from this particular
假设我不想检索一个字符，但我想从这个特定的字符串中检索一个子串。
string.
字符串。
Let's create a more bigger string. So, biggerString =
让我们创建一个更大的字符串。所以，biggerString =
"This is a lot of text". So, let's say I have this text in here
"这是个很大的文本"。所以，假设我有这个文本在这里
and from this I would want to get the substring starting from 'is', right.
我想从这里得到从 "是 "开始的子串，对。
So, I would want to get all the characters starting from here.
所以，我想获得从这里开始的所有字符。
How can I do that?
我怎样才能做到这一点呢？
Doing that is called a Substring. Substring methods accepts the index of this character.
这样做被称为Substring。子串方法接受这个字符的索引。
So, we would need to pass in the index of this character
所以，我们需要传入这个字符的索引
and it would be able to print the rest of the strings.
它就可以打印出其余的字符串了。
Let's do,
让我们来做。
biggerString. , I would want to do it from
biggerString. ，我想从
i. So, 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, and 5,
i. 所以，0、1、2、3、4和5。
biggerString.substring(5). So, it's printing "is a lot of text", right.
biggerString.substring(5)。所以，它在打印 "是很多的文本"，对。
So, that's how you do a substring. I'm trying to get a part of the string. Here
所以，这就是你做子串的方法。我试图得到字符串的一部分。这里
we are specifying the start of the string. But you can also specify start and end also. So, I'm specifying 5
我们指定的是字符串的开头。但你也可以指定开始和结束。所以，我指定5
as the start and I can specify okay, this is 5,
作为开始，我可以指定好，这是5。
I would want to get up to 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12. So, let's say, I would want to get up to t, t is at
我希望能达到6、7、8、9、10、11、12。所以，比方说，我想达到t，t是在
index 12. So, if you want to get up to character with index 12, then you need to enter 13.
索引12。所以，如果你想获得索引为12的字符，那么你需要输入13。
So, the important thing to understand is this side is inclusive,
所以，重要的是要明白，这一边是包容的。
this is exclusive.
这个是排他性的。
So, this index is not really included.
所以，这个索引并不真正包括在内。
So, the character at index 13 will not be part of the substring.
所以，索引13的字符不会成为子串的一部分。
So, the character at index 13, if we do it,
所以，索引13处的字符，如果我们这样做。
so if I do str.charAt(13), you would see that it returns a space back.
所以如果我做str.charAt(13)，你会看到它返回了一个空格。
Oops! I should have actually done biggerString.charAt(13). So, biggerString.charAt(13),
Oops! 我实际上应该做 biggerString.charAt(13)。所以，biggerString.charAt(13)。
it prints a space out.
它打印出了一个空格。
So, this is the space which is present at character 13 and that is not included in the string, because
所以，这是存在于字符13的空格，它不包括在字符串中，因为
this is exclusive.
这是排他性的。
So, starting from the character at index 5 to 12. So, it's when I pass in a 13, only the character
所以，从索引5到12的字符开始。所以，当我传入一个13时，只有索引12以下的字符
upto index 12 would be included in the substring.
会被包含在子串中。
I will recommend you to try and play around with these things charAt, substring and see what you can
我建议你尝试使用charAt, substring这些东西，看看你能找到什么。
find.
发现。
One interesting aspect is, if you try and give a index out of the range of the string, so let's say the
一个有趣的方面是，如果你试图给一个超出字符串范围的索引，那么我们假设
string is length 5 and you give an index of 15 then it would throw a StringIndexOutOfBoundsException.
字符串的长度是5，而你给出的索引是15，那么它就会抛出一个StringIndexOutOfBoundsException。
Exceptions are Java's way of telling you; Okay buddy,
异常是Java告诉你的方式；好了，伙计。
as a programmer you are doing something wrong, I'm throwing you an exception.
作为一个程序员，你做错了什么，我给你抛出一个异常。
How can I get the 10th character in a string of length 5? That's wrong.
我怎样才能在一个长度为5的字符串中获得第10个字符？这是不对的。
That's an exception.
这就是一个异常。
The same kind of exception would happen with charAt, if you do something invalid and the same thing
同样的异常会发生在charAt上，如果你做了一些无效的事情，同样的事情也会发生在
would happen with substring
也会发生在substring
also. So, if I say, charAt(456), 456 is an invalid index. So, it would throw you a IndexOutOfBoundsException.
也是如此。所以，如果我说，charAt(456)，456是一个无效的索引。所以，它会给你一个IndexOutOfBoundsException。
Okay. In this video, what we looked at is number one, we looked at the fact that every string literal is
好的，在这个视频中，我们看的是第一点，我们看的是每个字符串的字面意义是
an instance of a class.
是一个类的实例。
This is the only type of literal which is a instance of a specific class
这是唯一一种是特定类的实例的字面意义。
and also we discussed the fact that string is a special type, in the sense that we did not really need
我们还讨论了一个事实，即字符串是一个特殊的类型，在这个意义上，我们并不真的需要
to do a new string to create an instance of the string. All that you need to do is str1 =
来创建一个字符串的实例。你所需要做的就是str1 =
"SomeString" and Java would automatically create an object for you.
"SomeString"，Java会自动为你创建一个对象。
This is something unique to String and also we looked at and also we looked at a few important methods
这是字符串特有的东西，我们也看了一些重要的方法
substring and charAt. At the end of this video, we were introduced to a simple concept called exceptions
substring和charAt。在这个视频的最后，我们介绍了一个简单的概念，叫做异常。
which we will discuss a lot more in a separate section on exceptions.
我们将在关于异常的单独章节中讨论更多的内容。
I'll leave this video with an exercise.
我将以一个练习来离开这个视频。
So, let's say I have a string, right. So, let's say I have a very simple string, String someString =
那么，我们假设我有一个字符串，对。所以，让我们假设我有一个非常简单的字符串，String someString =
"This is a lot of text
"这又是一大堆的文字
again". What I would want to do is, write some code in here which would print individual characters on
又是"。我想做的是，在这里写一些代码，将单个字符打印在
separate lines. So, the output should be 't' on one line, 'h' on next line, 'i' on next line, 's' on next
单独的行。所以，输出应该是 "t "在一行，"h "在下一行，"i "在下一行，"s "在下一行。
line, and so on, and so forth.
行，以此类推。
We'll discuss the solution in the next video.
我们将在下一个视频中讨论这个解决方案。
Until then,
在那之前。
bye bye.
bye bye。